{"componentChunkName":"component---src-templates-establishment-page-js","path":"/establishment/513","result":{"data":{"site":{"pathPrefix":"/restaurant-inspections"},"postgres":{"establishment":[{"establishmentid":"513","name":"Subway Harbortown Detroit","address":"3424 Jefferson Ave. E.","zipcode":"48207","owner":"Aristidis Moschouris","licenseNumber":"034341","licenseType":"Fixed Establishment","establishmentType":"Food Service Establishment","establishmentStatus":"Open","riskCategory":null,"reviewFrequencyDays":"335","coords":"-83.01095,42.34297","geojson":{"id":"513","type":"Feature","geometry":{"type":"Point","coordinates":[-83.010945565,42.342965404]},"properties":{"name":"Subway Harbortown Detroit","owner":"Aristidis Moschouris","address":"3424 Jefferson Ave. E.","zipcode":"48207","license_type":"Fixed Establishment","risk_category":null,"license_number":"034341","establishmentid":"513","establishment_type":"Food Service Establishment","establishment_status":"Open","review_frequency_days":"335","most_recent_license_date":"2022-04-19"}},"nearbyList":[{"establishmentid":"503","name":"Peking Express","address":"3444 Jefferson Ave. E.","zipcode":"48207"},{"establishmentid":"3884","name":"Real Bar B Q ","address":"3496 Jefferson Ave. E.","zipcode":"48207"},{"establishmentid":"651","name":"Harbortown Pizza & Subs Inc. d/b/a Jet's","address":"3420 Jefferson Ave. E.","zipcode":"48207"},{"establishmentid":"2990","name":"Michigan Commission for the Blind","address":"333 Mt. Elliott","zipcode":"48207"},{"establishmentid":"51623733","name":"Streetcredit Coworking & Events LLC","address":"6340 Jefferson E.","zipcode":"48207"},{"establishmentid":"2764","name":"Little Caesar's Pizza #164","address":"500 Mt. Elliott","zipcode":"48207"},{"establishmentid":"3305","name":"Quizno's","address":"500 Mt. Elliott","zipcode":"48207"},{"establishmentid":"3203","name":"Happy's Pizza #11","address":"6412  Jefferson Ave. E.","zipcode":"48207"},{"establishmentid":"4264","name":"Zen Bar & Restaurant","address":"6452 E. Jefferson","zipcode":"48207"},{"establishmentid":"51622615","name":"Le Petit Dejeuner","address":"6470  E. Jefferson","zipcode":"48207"}],"inspectionsByEstablishmentidList":[{"inspectionid":"60599","inspectionDate":"2022-09-19T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"2-402.11","violationDescription":"FOOD EMPLOYEES shall wear hair restraints such as hats, hair coverings or nets, beard restraints, and clothing that covers body hair, that are designed and worn to effectively keep their hair from contacting exposed FOOD; clean EQUIPMENT, UTENSILS, and LINENS; or unwrapped SINGLE-SERVICE or SINGLE-USE ARTICLES.","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":null,"subItem":"","problemDescription":null,"subProblem":"","location":"RESTAURANT","subLocation":"","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"2-402.11","violationDescription":"FOOD EMPLOYEES shall wear hair restraints such as hats, hair coverings or nets, beard restraints, and clothing that covers body hair, that are designed and worn to effectively keep their hair from contacting exposed FOOD; clean EQUIPMENT, UTENSILS, and LINENS; or unwrapped SINGLE-SERVICE or SINGLE-USE ARTICLES.","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Hair restraint","subItem":"hair/beard net","problemDescription":"Not worn on face","subProblem":"","location":"RESTAURANT","subLocation":"Missing Beard Net","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Provide beard net."},{"violationCode":"4-204.11","violationDescription":"Exhaust ventilation hood systems in FOOD preparation and WAREWASHING areas including components such as hoods, fans, guards, and ducting shall be designed to prevent grease or condensation from draining or dripping onto FOOD, EQUIPMENT, UTENSILS, LINENS, and SINGLE-SERVICE and SINGLE-USE ARTICLES.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Exhaust ventilation hood system(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Designed to allow grease or condensation from draining/dripping onto","subProblem":"Equipment","location":"FRONT PREP AREA","subLocation":"Missing FILTERS","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Repair/replace to prevent grease accumulation/dripping/draining."}]},{"inspectionid":"56130","inspectionDate":"2021-09-30T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[]},{"inspectionid":"52685","inspectionDate":"2020-09-09T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"5-205.11","violationDescription":"(A) A HANDWASHING SINK shall be maintained so that it is accessible at all times for EMPLOYEE use and used for no other purpose. (Pf)\n(B)  An automatic handwashing facility shall be used in accordance with manufacturer's instructions. (Pf)\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Handwashing sink(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not easily accessible","subProblem":"Items stored On","location":"REAR AREA","subLocation":"At the Handsink","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2020-09-10T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Remove items from handsink.  Do not store items at handsink."}]},{"inspectionid":"46066","inspectionDate":"2019-05-05T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"No","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"4-501.11","violationDescription":"EQUIPMENT shall be maintained in a state of repair and condition that meets the requirements of the code.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Equipment","subItem":"","problemDescription":"In poor repair","subProblem":"","location":"FRONT COUNTER/AREA","subLocation":"At the Cooler (2 door)","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"5-205.15","violationDescription":"A PLUMBING SYSTEM shall be:\n(A) Repaired according to LAW; (P) and\n(B) Maintained in good repair.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Plumbing system","subItem":"water line(s)","problemDescription":"Not maintained","subProblem":"","location":"REAR PREP AREA","subLocation":"At the Handsink","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null}]},{"inspectionid":"46067","inspectionDate":"2019-05-05T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Complaint","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[]},{"inspectionid":"43088","inspectionDate":"2018-08-06T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"4-501.11","violationDescription":"EQUIPMENT shall be maintained in a state of repair and condition that meets the requirements of the code.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Equipment components","subItem":"","problemDescription":null,"subProblem":"","location":"FRONT PREP AREA","subLocation":"At the Oven (Bread)","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"6-501.14","violationDescription":"(A) Intake and exhaust air ducts shall be cleaned and filters changed so they are not a source of contamination by dust, dirt, and other materials. \n(B) If vented to the outside, ventilation systems may not create a public health HAZARD or nuisance or unLAWful discharge.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Ventilation system","subItem":"exhaust air ducts","problemDescription":"Not clean","subProblem":"","location":"FRONT PREP AREA","subLocation":"At the Ductwork","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Clean"}]},{"inspectionid":"39491","inspectionDate":"2017-08-01T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"6-501.12","violationDescription":"(A) PHYSICAL FACILITIES shall be cleaned as often as necessary to keep them clean.\n(B) Except spill cleanup, cleaning shall be done during periods when the least amount of FOOD is exposed such as after closing. ","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Physical facilities/structures","subItem":"ceiling","problemDescription":"Soiled","subProblem":"","location":"LOBBY/ (Customer Waiting Area)","subLocation":"On the Ceiling (s)","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Keep clean."}]},{"inspectionid":"36204","inspectionDate":"2016-08-21T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"4-602.13","violationDescription":"NonFOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of EQUIPMENT shall be cleaned at a frequency necessary to preclude accumulation of soil residues.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Nonfood contact surface(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Soiled","subProblem":"","location":"ENTIRE FACILITY","subLocation":"At the Equipment","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Keep clean."},{"violationCode":"4-202.18","violationDescription":"Filters or other grease extracting EQUIPMENT shall be designed to be readily removable for cleaning and replacement if not designed to be cleaned in place.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Ventilation hood filter(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":null,"subProblem":"","location":"FRONT PREP AREA","subLocation":"Missing FILTERS","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null}]}]}],"maxInspectionDate":[{"inspectionDate":"2023-04-25T00:00:00"}]}},"pageContext":{"eid":"513"}},"staticQueryHashes":["3649515864","63159454"]}